<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ScrollView xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    xmlns:app="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res-auto"
    xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools"
    android:layout_width="match_parent"
    android:layout_height="match_parent"
    app:layout_behavior="@string/appbar_scrolling_view_behavior"
    tools:context=".AvisoActivity"
    tools:showIn="@layout/app_bar_aviso">

    <TextView
        android:id="@+id/textView"
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
        android:text="Privacy Policy\nWe value your comments, suggestions and feedback. Our Privacy Policy sets out how we collect, use and disclose “personal information” and other “non personal\ninformation” we have gathered about you.\n\nWhat is Personal Information and why do we collect it from you?\n\n‘Personal Information’ is information or an opinion that identifies you as an individual.\nWe collect and store your email when you sign up for our newsletter, or where you \nnominate to specifically allow our games to collect your email. If you contact us \ndirectly for any reason, we may also keep a copy of that correspondence. Your email is \ncollected only to keep you informed of new products and changes to our existing \nproducts.\n\nNewsletter\n\nWhen you elect to join our mailing list for the purpose of receiving our newsletter we \nmay use that “personal information” to provide you with direct marketing \ncommunications about upcoming games, features of our websites and other events and \npromotions related to our products. You may unsubscribe from our newsletter at any \ntime. All you need to do is unsubscribe from the link in the letter, or let us know in\nwriting that you want to be removed.\n\nSensitive Information\n\nSensitive information is defined in the US Privacy Act (1974) to include information or\nopinion about such things as an individual’s racial or ethnic origin, political opinions, \nmembership of a political association, religious or philosophical beliefs, membership of\na professional body, criminal records or health information.\nWe will not attempt to obtain nor record any sensitive information.\n\nDisclosure of Personal Information\n\nWe will not sell, trade, rent or disclose any of the personal information you provide to\n us for any reason, without your prior consent. Otherwise, your Personal Information\nwill only be disclosed where required or allowable by law.\n\nSecurity of Personal Information\n\nYour Personal Information is stored offsite in a manner that reasonably protects it from\nmisuse, loss, unauthorized access, modification or disclosure.\nWe don’t guarantee website links or policy of authorised third parties and you access\nthose sites at your own risk.\n\nAccess to your Personal Information\n\nUnder the Privacy Act, NPP 6 gives you the right to access the Personal Information we\nhold about you and to update and/or correct it, subject to certain exceptions. If you wish\nto access your Personal Information, please make out your request to us in writing at the\naddress listed below. We will not charge any fee for your access request, but may\ncharge an administrative fee.Please be aware that in order to protect the Personal\nInformation in our database, we will require identification from you before releasing\nmany information.\n\nCollection of other ‘Non-Personal’ Information\n\nThough we don’t use cookies in order to track your movement around the web, our\nwebsites and apps may contain APIs from third parties. Specifically, Helpify websites\nuse Google Analytics to help analyse how users use the site. The tool uses cookies to\ncollect internet log information and visitor behaviour information in an anonymous \nform. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website, including\nyour IP address, is transmitted to Google. This information is then used to evaluate use\nof our website and to compile statistical reports on website activity.\n\nOur third party partners, and their privacy policies are as follows:\n\nAdmob (Google):\nGoogle Analytics:\n\nPolicy Updates\n\nThis Policy may change from time to time.\n\nWe will always keep this up to date so that you know what information we will collect \nfrom you, how we may use it, and when we may disclose it.\n\nComplaints\n\nYou can lodge a complaint with us about any breach of our Privacy Policy at the address below. " />
</ScrollView>